by H.
ME
The group Uka is a six-member idol group.
Uka, a six-member idol group
Uka is a junior group of Momokuro and Ellis Junior High School, and is a hot group with nostalgic, sweet and sour songs like those from a coming-of-age novel.
Uka has been filming a music video for a new song while enjoying the city of Osaka.
This time we visited Nakazaki-cho, a town that represents Osaka's retro atmosphere.
The next spot, a somewhat nostalgic and nostalgic spot, is a general store called Orinpepe-san.
The shop is a psychedelic and pop sundries store that has evolved uniquely in Japan based on the concept of "me Showa-era everything store".
It is a store that deals in clothing.
We came up with this project!
A fashion showdown!
Yay!
Who would like to challenge me?
Well, maybe two people.
Who wants to do it?
Okay.
I'll do it.
What? What?
The other is 17-year-old Moa Serizawa, the youngest in the group.
Both of them call themselves Uguka's fashion leaders.
Who will show us the fashionable foursome that fits the somewhat nostalgic theme of the location?
This is the one I'm looking at right now.
This is what I like to do when I'm at Castaic food.
It's like you can put boiling water and ice in it and it won't end.
It's great.
What do you think?
It's the most standard.
Good luck. Be careful.
Are you guys watching?
Hey, you okay?
Serizawa Moi, who is conscious of total coordination based on denim.
and Yukirina, who loves to show off and collects bright items.
How did it turn out?
The original Yukirina
Well then, it looks like we're ready to go!
Rina, Moa, you ready?
Yes!
Yes! I got it.
This one's in.
It's so good! It's so good!
So, what's the point?
Well, I often show my belly in my clothes.
So I wore this retro dress with my belly showing.
I hope you can feel the retro atmosphere by wearing a scarf.
No, it's much better than I thought it would be.
And the horns, too... and here, we've added a bit of yellow...
Now, Rina Yuki, the Hashi Oda in question, please.
What do you think, Rina?
Ta-da!
I saw this one first and thought it was so cool!
Lavender, I found red on my mother and other people, and I love red...
I found this yellow one and thought it was soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo cute!
The most important thing to keep in mind is that you should not be afraid to use ketchup on your eggs.
If you think Cerizamo's corset was good...
Seino
Yes!
Thank you very much!
And that's that.
Selizer Mo-chan wins!Cerizamo won!
Yay!
Thanks for the okra.
I'd like to give you my prize, okra.
Okra!
And that's the end of the location.
And now, your wait is over.
Now on sale.
Music video for Blow Up Days from Ukka's first debut single
Blow Up Days music video
Please take a look at the episode version.
We are waiting for you!
S resistance Tsukushi
Two tiny 16 year olds
We melted softly, softly, softly, softly in the sky at 26:00.
Always pretending to be nice, we hid our true selves.
Before we knew it, we started smiling the way we want to.
I got good at smiling, and I even got hurt.
I wonder if I'll grow up to be a boring adult without realizing it.
Next time...
I'll walk my own way, even if it's filled with love every day.
I don't care if it's a clumsy way to live, I like the way I am now.
I gently and softly wrap up the feelings in my chest that are about to overflow
I'll raise the voice in my heart that I've been hiding and become an adult
It's alright
On the contrary, can I ask you to tell me why you didn't choose Rina?
You don't like the fact that the first button is open?
There!
When it's closed...
That's right.
Let's close it.